I was the one who was lost in the gray A ship in the
dark, afraid of the day You were the harbor, the
only truth My anchor in this crazy youth But an
anchor's made to hold you fast
It was never meant to make you last I'm here,
holding you down Afraid that you would leave
this town But you were never meant to stay You
were A sailman to fly away And I was just the heavy
stone The one you had to leave alone Now I'm the
anchor And you're the sail Little
Johnny can sail
I'm not a stone, I'm by your side We're in this
current, on the same tide I'm not the anchor, I'm
the wind The one who helps your journey begin
We're not an anchor and a sail We're just a ship
that will prevail We are the compass, we are the
map We're finding our way back
Cause you were never meant to stay You were the
sail Meant to fly But I was never a heavy stone You
never had to be alone I'm not the anchor You're
not the sail We're in this storm and we will
prevail
We will prevail
We're coming home